http://www.tuscl.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
We have developed this policy in order for you to understand how we collect and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
For non members, we collect no personal information. We may collect your ip address and location lattitude and longitude of that IP address.
For members, we collect an email address, nickname, and password.
We may also collect your ip address and location lattitude and longitude of that IP address.
For members who join with a credit card, all information regarding your credit card (Name, Number, Type, Exp Date, etc) is passed straight to our credit card processors, where they store your information on their secured servers.
TUSCL does not store any personal credit card information.
We do not distribute your email addresses, nicknames, or any other data to any other company. We respect your anonimity.
We do, however, reserve the right to publish all the personal information we have about you.
We will make available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We will cooperate fully with law enforcement regarding sex trafficking, harrasment, or any other offences.
We make no claim that we conduct our business in order to guarantee that your personal information is protected.
closehomeHomelocal_barListingslocal_playReviewsmenu_bookDancersmy_locationLocationsphoto_cameraPhoto Gallerylibrary_booksArticlesforumDiscussionsgroupGroupsadd_businessAdd a Listingperson_addJoinloginLogin
Login
Join
searchclose
